## **ISABELLA NUNES**

### **Software Developer**

- @ isadfrn@gmail.com

  isadfrn in isadfrn
- Blumenau, SC, Brazil
- www.isadfrn.dev



### **ABOUT**

Software Developer who likes Algorithms, Data Structures, Linux, Open Source projects, and teaching code. Worked on big projects and interacted with people from many places. Likes to learn, be part of challenging projects, and deal with technologies, and persons. Also, it teaches code for beginners who want to learn how to program for more than seven years. Experience in Full-Stack development, building a career with a T-shaped approach with depth in back-end development.

### **EXPERIENCE**

### Software Developer

#### **Philips**

Dec 2020 - Ongoing

Blumenau, SC, Brazil

#### Main activities:

- Building and maintaining microservices and internal tools;
- Working on healthcare projects, interacting with USA, India, and Netherlands teams;
- Agile team working with Scaled Agile Framework (SAFe) using Azure DevOps for management;
- Stack and tools: Java, Kotlin, Spring Framework, PL/SQL, Oracle Database, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, JUnit, Mockito, Docker, Kafka, Jenkins, GitHub Actions, Sonar, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, React.js, Angular, and SharePoint;
- Systems: Philips Tasy;

### **Programming Instructor**

### **Digital House Brasil**

Jun 2022 - Ongoing

São Paulo, SP, Brazil

### Main activities:

- Instructor of JavaScript, Node.js, Express.js, SQL, MySQL, Sequelize, HTML, CSS, EJS, and React.js;
- Working on educational sector projects;
- Preparation of code projects and documentation;

### **Programming Instructor**

#### Blue EdTech

**May 2021 - Jun 2022** 

São Paulo, SP, Brazil

#### Main activities:

- Instructor of JavaScript, TypeScript, Node.js, Express.js, HTML, CSS, React.js, NestJS, Next.js, Prisma, Mongoose, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, and Docker;
- Working on educational sector projects;
- Preparation of code projects and documentation;

### MY LIFE PHILOSOPHY

"If you can't do it, practice until you can. If you can do it, practice until you can do it perfectly. If you can do it perfectly, practice until you can do it perfectly every time."

### **MOST PROUD OF**



#### **Academic Tutor**

In college I was monitor of Algorithms II, Data Structures I, Data Structures II, Software Engineer, Software Project and Computer Organization

### **STRENGTHS**

Hard-wor	king Eye for detail	
Resilient	Self-learner Communication	on
Java	otlin JavaScript Python	
Java Ko		

### **LANGUAGES**

Portuguese	Native
English	C1

### **EDUCATION**

### PgD in Java

Federal University of Technology - Parana

**Mar 2022 - Jul 2023** 

# B.Sc. in Computer Science Federal University of Goiás

Feb 2014 - Dec 2018

### Software Developer

### Nutrien Soluções Agrícolas

**J**ul 2020 - Apr 2021

Rio Verde, GO, Brazil

#### Main activities:

- Building and maintaining integration systems;
- Working on agriculture sector projects;
- Agile team working with Kanban using Jira for management;
- Stack and tools: Java, JavaScript, Python, PL/SQL, AdvPL, Django, Node.js, React.js, React Native, PyQt, MongoDB, MySQL, PostgreSQL, Oracle Database, Docker, Portainer, and Kubernetes;
- Systems: Totvs Protheus, Senior, Simple Sync, Simple Field, Simple Sales, and Fretefy;

### **Programming Instructor**

#### Senac

**May 2015 - Dec 2020** 

Jataí, GO, Brazil

#### Main activities:

- Instructor of Java, Visual Basic for Applications, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Microsoft Excel;
- Working on educational sector projects
- Preparation of code projects and documentation;

### Junior Software Developer

#### J. Cruzeiro

**i** Jul 2018 - Jul 2020

Jataí, GO, Brazil

#### Main activities:

- Building and maintaining websites, systems, and indoor infrastructure;
- Working on construction industry projects;
- Stack and tools: Java, Spring Framework, PL/SQL, Oracle Database, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, and React.js;
- Systems: ADM (Santri Sistemas), Senior, Sienge, Linx Degust,
   Zabbix, Windows Server, Active Directory, Samba, Citrix XenServer,
   XenApp, XenDesktop, Director, Netscaler, pfSense, Sophos XG,
   and Openfire Spark;
- Hardware: UTM Sophos, IBM Flex System x240, IBM DS4200, IBM V3700, IBM Tivoli, and IBM TSM3100;

### A DAY OF MY LIFE

